{
  "NITPQ1": {
    "name": "Sam's Pub Quiz",
    "rounds": [
      {
        "name": "Current Affairs",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What does COVID-19 stand for?",
            "answer": "I don't know.",
            "points": 2
          },
          {
            "question": "What does COVID-19 stand for?",
            "answer": "I don't know.",
            "points": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "More Current Affairs",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What does COVID-19 stand for?",
            "answer": "I don't know.",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What does COVID-19 stand for?",
            "answer": "I don't know.",
            "points": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "id": "NITPQ1",
    "host_id": "NITPQ1",
    "teams": [
      {
        "id": "TEAM1",
        "name": "I lost my job and now all I do is host this quiz",
        "answers": [
          [
            "Answer",
            "Also An Answer"
          ],
          [
            "",
            ""
          ]
        ],
        "scores": [
          [
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0
          ]
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": "TEAM2",
        "name": "Team 2",
        "answers": [
          [
            "Wrong Answer",
            "What is Covid?"
          ],
          [
            "",
            ""
          ]
        ],
        "scores": [
          [
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0
          ]
        ]
      }
    ],
    "state": "pre-quiz",
    "current_round": 0,
    "current_question": -1,
    "options": {
      "allow_signups": false
    }
  },
  "XXKQIK": {
    "id": "XXKQIK",
    "host_id": "OUNBKBUWQSBH1QREB90D",
    "name": "Postgrads Lockdown Quiz",
    "rounds": [
      {
        "name": "Working From Home",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Archaeologist",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Pilot",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Zookeeper",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Taxi Driver",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Demolition Worker",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Truck driver",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Builder",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Receptionist",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Train conductor",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the occupation",
            "answer": "Surgeon",
            "points": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Fictional Pub",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the pub in the Disney film Tangled?",
            "answer": "The Snuggly Duckling",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the pub in Coronation Street?",
            "answer": "Rovers Return Inn",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the pub in the Carry On films?",
            "answer": "The Whippit Inn",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the pub in Eastenders?",
            "answer": "The Queen Victoria",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where can you drink Butterbeer in Hogsmeade?",
            "answer": "Three Broomsticks ",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is Homer Simpson's favourite pub?",
            "answer": "Moe's Tavern",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the pub in the Lord of the Rings: Fellowship of the Ring?",
            "answer": "The Prancing Pony",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "In \"The World's End\", what are the names of the ninth and twelfth pubs on the Golden Mile pub crawl?",
            "answer": "The Beehive and The World's End",
            "points": 2
          },
          {
            "question": "What's the pub where everybody knows your name?",
            "answer": "Cheers",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where would you go to have a nice cold pint, and wait for all this to blow over?",
            "answer": "Winchester Arms",
            "points": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Disney",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What is the address Dory has to remember in Finding Nemo?",
            "answer": "P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What was the first feature-length Disney movie?",
            "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What fraction will you find on the Mad Hatter's hat?",
            "answer": "10/6",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What was the name of the town Rapunzel lived in in Tangled?",
            "answer": "Corona",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Who created Pinocchio?",
            "answer": "Geppetto",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Name the 3 good fairies in Sleeping Beauty",
            "answer": "Flora, Fauna & Merryweather",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is the only Disney song to have won a Grammy for ‘song of the year’?",
            "answer": "A Whole New World",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is Boo’s real name in Monster’s Inc?",
            "answer": "Mary",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "How many eggs does Gaston eat for breakfast?",
            "answer": "Five dozen (60!)",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Name all of the Seven Dwarfs",
            "answer": " Dopey, Sneezy, Bashful, Doc, Happy, Grumpy & Sleepy",
            "points": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Back to the Nineties ",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Saved by the bell",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Pinky and the brain",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Hey Arnold",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Keenan and Kel",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Rugrats",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Recess",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Friends",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Fraiser",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Dawson's creek",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Guess the theme tune",
            "answer": "Gladiator",
            "points": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Bored Games",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What is the first property after passing go in Monopoly?",
            "answer": "Old Kent Road",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "How many points would the word 'Scrabble' get you in a game of Scrabble?",
            "answer": "14",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which chess piece (aside from a Queen) allows you to move diagonally?",
            "answer": "Bishop",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where in the body could you find a horse in Operation?",
            "answer": "Leg",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "How many territories are there in Risk?",
            "answer": "44",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Aside from the career path, which path can you take in the Game of Life?",
            "answer": "College",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What colour is the 'Science and Nature' category in Trivial Pursuit?",
            "answer": "Green",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "In which game would you find the card \"Why am I sticky?\"",
            "answer": "Cards against Humanity",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which part of your body is the plastic piece for in Speak Out?",
            "answer": "Mouth",
            "points": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "In which game do you work as a team to treat infections around the world?",
            "answer": "Pandemic",
            "points": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "teams": [
      {
        "id": "WNEGU4JV5V",
        "name": "Quizteam Quarantino",
        "answers": [
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ]
        ],
        "scores": [
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ]
        ],
        "connected": false
      },
      {
        "id": "DH7ADOKA51",
        "name": "Quizanderthals ",
        "answers": [
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ]
        ],
        "scores": [
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ]
        ],
        "connected": false
      },
      {
        "id": "TOJ8PI591I",
        "name": "Quaran-Tina Turner",
        "answers": [
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ]
        ],
        "scores": [
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ]
        ],
        "connected": false
      },
      {
        "id": "QMFUS0CRUO",
        "name": "Quaranation Street",
        "answers": [
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ]
        ],
        "scores": [
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ]
        ],
        "connected": false
      },
      {
        "id": "EONMWFBTRO",
        "name": "",
        "answers": [
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ]
        ],
        "scores": [
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ]
        ],
        "connected": false
      }
    ],
    "options": {
      "save_quiz": true,
      "allow_signups": true
    },
    "state": "pre-quiz",
    "current_round": -1,
    "current_question": -1,
    "connected_teams": 0,
    "connected_players": 0
  }
}